Good man. I grew up in a very very u
religious conservative household,
Southern Baptist, and now my mom uh
talks in tongues. And uh that's true. Uh
and uh I I like to think that I can kind
of say whatever I want to about about
the religious south because my last name
is
Cash. Uh my mom talks in tongues and my
dad worked on a pit crew when they still
raced NASCAR on dirt.
So, that's a redneck resume. Strong
enough to say whatever I want to. And if
you get mad, we're probably cousins and
we'll figure it out after the show. All
right. Try to
relax. My mom's super religious. I uh I
I joke with her because in the South,
people use religion a little
differently. Uh we use our Christian
beliefs to explain things that make us
sad. You know, like somebody will just
be like, "Well, I got a flat tire on the
way to work today. I guess God just did
not want me to be there on
time." It's probably what it was,
Karen. Either that or you just ran over
a nail. That's a distinct possibility.
Let's not rule it out. Think God was up
in heaven like, "Guys, get in here. I'm
about to mess with Karen again." She
didn't pray hard enough. She's about to
get a flat tire on her Pontiac vibe.
such a ridiculous thing, you
know, people, that's how that's how they
explain things in the south. Like, uh, I
I come from a NASCAR kind of family, as
I mentioned, and when Dale Earnhard
passed away, I mean, it was like a day
of mourning in the town I grew up in.
People were so sad. But all the
Southerners in my little town, they all
got together with one unified message.
You know, everybody went out and got
that that sticker for the back of the PT
Cruiser with the number three on it with
the halo and the
wings and just said, "God needed a
driver." Is that what it was? God just
up in heaven like, "Guys, get in here. I
need a driver. I want to go fast in
circles."
No, I know we already got a driver. I
want Dale Nhard. Number three, the
ginger with the mustache. Get him up
here. Stat. I know there's a race going
on. I'm watching it. That's what made me
think of this. Okay. I don't know. Crash
him. Just get him up
here. It's crazy, man. It was It wasn't
just rednecks. Some of my black
girlfriends did the same thing on
Twitter when Whitney Houston passed
away. They were like, uh, # Whitney,
#
sad, # Houston, we have a
problem. And they were like, Whitney's
up in heaven singing with the angels.
She's the lead singer of the angels.
She's the choir director in heaven. And
it made me feel better cuz I was bummed
cuz I mean, what a talented musician she
was, you know? It gave me like a warm
feeling there for a minute and then I
was like, you know, lead singer of the
Angels seems like a pretty important
job. That probably requires a drug test.
I'm
thinking, you know, I don't want to be
presumptuous. I'm just thinking if I got
to be in a cup to work at Liberty Tax,
God's probably not handing out jobs to
people with substance abuse problems.
Uh, don't have Liberty Tax here.
Oh man, what a great company. Do you
know what I'm talking about? Liberty
Tax. Yeah. Who's Who's getting their
taxes done there? That's I want to meet
those people. Like, who is their gorilla
marketing working on? Who's driving by
Liberty Tax being like, "Look there,
honey. I really respect this company for
dressing up drunk homeless people as a
Statue of Liberty. I think I want them
to handle all of my financial
information. Let's just whip on in
there. Give them our social security
number. What could go wrong?
So crazy to
me. I love those sign people, man. The
mattress sale or whatever, you know,
like, how do you get that job? Like,
what's the interview? They're like, "Uh,
are you wasted?" Yes, sir. I'm
wasted. Can you do the running man and
the cabbage patch at the same time? Oh,
yes, sir. I'm pretty good
dancer. That's what they're always
doing. They always got the sign. They're
always doing the running man and the
cabbage patch. It's like
Isn't they
twirling? Oh, no. Don't clap for that.
That does not deserve clapping. Now I'm
all winded cuz I'm out of shape. That
was cardio for
me. Oh
man. My mom's a very religious woman.
Sweetest woman alive. Very, very
religious. She goes to two different
churches. Um, one of them is the the
tongue-talking church and they do a
prayer call where they all get on the
phone and they all make those sounds
together and
uh it's terrifying.
[Applause]
Um, and they do communion while on the
prayer call. They're like and then they
take a cracker. And so anyway, I kind of
forgot about that. I tour all the time
and I don't live with my mom but I visit
her for extend extended periods of time
often in between comedy cuz my wife left
and
so I so I I'm coming off tour. I've been
in the car for like 10 hours and
sometimes I try not to drink a whole lot
when I'm in the car because I don't want
to have to use the bathroom, you know?
So, I get to her house and I'm just like
parched. I'm like completely like so so
thirsty. And I open the refrigerator and
she's in the living room like on the
other side of the kitchen. Open the
refrigerator and eye level is this big
bottle of grape juice. And I'm like,
"Yeah, I'm about to crush that." And by
the way, grape juice, does anybody ever
buy that? Anybody ever buy grape juice?
Nobody ever buys grape juice, but it's
everywhere. They're still in business. I
think it's a front for some kind of drug
cartel or something.
They got commercials, billboards,
trucks, a big distribution system.
Nobody buys it. Nobody in here's ever
bought it ever
once. But I see it on the shelf staring
at me. I'm like, "Oh yeah, this is about
to happen." And so I just take and I'm
just taking it to the face just like and
it's so good. It's just that sweet
Concord grape nectar. And then I start
thinking like this is her house. That
was rude of me to just drink it out of
the bottle without even asking, you
know? So, I stop and I'm like, "Hey,
Mom." She's like, "Yeah." It's like,
"Can I drink this grape juice?" She gets
quiet for a minute and then she says,
"Well, I had that for my
communion." And I was like, "Oh." And I
was like, "Well, I don't want to drink
all the
blood." And I and I thought she was
going to get mad at me. And then all of
a sudden, she goes, "There's some
crackers in there, too, if you want some
of the blood.
It's
weird. It's the funniest thing she's
ever said.
So, you're not holding back your last
for me. You're holding back for my mom.
And it's good. My mom uh it's just my
mom now. Um my dad passed away. It was
like one of the hardest things. If
you've lost a parent, you know how hard
it is. But it was really tough. And uh
we didn't see it coming. And it happened
really fast. And the thing about my dad,
the thing that made it extra hard, my
dad was just like the best guy in the
world. I mean, just the best guy you
ever met. Just kind and and humble and
and quiet and selfless and, you know,
he's always doing something for other
people. He never complained, never
bought himself anything, never wanted
for anything. Just like totally calm
water, you
know. Still winded. And
uh the only thing he would ever complain
about every once in a while when my mom
would leave the room, like on the
holidays, he would lean forward and he
would look at me and my brother and my
sister and he would make sure she was
gone and he would go, "Y'all think we
got enough knickknacks in
here?" Because my mom's a 75year-old
white lady who lives at the beach and
she loves knickknacks. I mean, just
everywhere. It's nice. It's not
horriish. It's very clean, but it's just
seashells and pelicans and lighthouses
and sailboats and flipflops and bird
bass and it's live, laugh, love, dance
like no one's watching, you know? It's a
lot
of it's a lot of that.
And and my dad, I think he probably just
sat back in his recliner and looked
around the house. It was like $50,
$80, $150,
$65. That was only a dollar because it
was from Ross Dress for last $80, you
know. He just he's like, "We got
$200,000 worth of nonsense in this
house." It was the only thing that drove
him crazy. He was still a good sport
about it, you know. He would kind of
nudge me and be like, "Think I've got
enough items on every surface of the
[Music]
house?" It's crazy. It's like if you're
going to set your lighthouse cut coaster
down, you're going to have to move the
southern living over by the coastal
living. And then you got to move those
mard duck playing cards over by the swan
with the fake flowers in it and push
those over by the sand dollars and the
metal starfish, you know, and then you
can put it put the lighthouse cup down
on the flip-flop coaster. And it's nice.
It's all very cute and nice. It's just a
lot of it, you know. And I think my dad
was like, "Why you got to put all this
stuff on the table? It's already a
dolphin. The table is a dolphin. Why do
you have to decorate a
decoration? But when my dad passed, my
mom sat us down and she said,
"Listen, it happened fast." She was
like, "You know, I just I don't know
what to do. I I just want to I just want
to get him cremated so I can kind of
have time to think about what to do. I
don't I'm just
overwhelmed." And we said, "Mom, we
support you like no matter what, you
know, whatever you need to do, we got
your back." And she was like, you know,
and I want to get him a really beautiful
earn. And I was like, well, mom, you
know, dad was a simple guy. He never
spent money on anything for himself. He
was really frugal and modest. He would
have wanted you to save that money. Get
him a simple earn and save that money
for something important like pelicans
and sailboats, you
know? She was like, "No, I want to get
him a nice earn." So, we did. We got
him. It is beautiful. Beautiful urns.
Very nautical. It's
kind It's this blue green. It's got some
like burlap kind of rope around and it's
got a piece of driftwood on the top of
the lid. And it's very coastal. And it
has little tiny It's clay. It's a
ceramics piece. Has little baby sea
turtles going all the way up the urn.
Beautiful piece. And we have it sitting
on a table in the living room with a
sailboat, metal sailboat hanging behind
it and a conch shell to the left of it
and this little palm tree thing to the
right of it. He became a knickknack is
what I'm trying to tell you. And it's
like the only thing he didn't want to
be, you know, just circle of
life. I feel like he's up in heaven
like, are you kidding
me? Guys, thank you so much. Y'all been
great. I love you. Have a good night.
[Applause]